<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Rag>
   <Article>
     <Magazine> Web Techniques Magazine </Magazine>
     <IssueDate> March  1998 </IssueDate>
     <Headline>Database Developer</Headline> 
     <Deck>New Servers, New Architectures, and Logic in the Database</Deck>
     <Byline> By Ken North</Byline>

     <ArticleText>
	If you are a Web developer faced with creating database-enabled pages, 
	or a database developer faced with building Web-enabled applications, 
	you have probably experienced the phenomenon known as "Web time." The 
	computer industry has never been quiet, but recent years have been 
	particularly frenetic. The popularity of the Web produced a flurry of 
	software-development activity....

     <Subhead ID="HEAD1">Application Architecture, Database Architecture</Subhead>
	In the mainframe era, database applications were often monolithic executables. 
	Operating-system improvements and modular programming brought dynamic linking 
	and shared libraries. Subsequent developments continued the trend of 
	distributing the logic of database applications. 

     <Subhead ID="HEAD2">Logic in the Database</Subhead>
	Because data integrity is a primary concern of database developers, DBMS vendors 
	provide several techniques for controlling how a DBMS manages data. These include 
	constraints, procedures, triggers, functions and packages. Some SQL dialects also 
	provide rules and a <CODE>CREATE</CODE> <CODE>RULE</CODE> statement. 

     </ArticleText>

     <BIOGRAPHY>
	<Author>Ken North</Author> is a software consultant who also writes and teaches 
	seminars. His 1998 projects include <Book>Database Magic with Ken North</Book>, 
	<Book>Java Database Magic with Ken North</Book> (<Publisher>Prentice-Hall 
	PTR</Publisher>), and Expert Series seminars.
     </BIOGRAPHY>

   </Article>

   <Article>

     <Magazine> Wit Mag </Magazine>
     <IssueDate> August  1998 </IssueDate>
     <Headline>XML Developer</Headline> 
     <Deck>New Techniques, New Things, and All that kind of stuf</Deck>
     <Byline> By J. Steve Witt</Byline>

     <ArticleText>
	Just testing to see if we can loop through this file and read all of the articles in it.
     </ArticleText>

     <BIOGRAPHY>
	<Author>Steve Witt</Author> is a senior software engineer who also writes and teaches 
	subjects on the Bible. His 1998 projects include <Book>Tabernacle Patterns</Book>, 
	<Book>Revelation with the Tabernacle</Book>, and ACTS seminars.
     </BIOGRAPHY>

   </Article>
</Rag>